A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 2010-2013
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 2010-2013
The Library of Virginia
51127
8.4 cu. ft (24 boxes)
Virginia. Office of the Secretary of Health and Human Resources
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and confidential information is restricted from public access for 75 years (Code of Virginia 42.1-78). Restricted records in this collection have been flagged but not removed. Types of flagged information may include, but is not limited to: medical records, financial records, vital statistics records, personal information including Social Security numbers, Social Services records, juvenile court records, administrative investigation records, attorney-client privileged documents, personnel records, proprietary information, and terrorism information and response records. Some documents may be closed in their entirety, while others may allow for redaction.
Acquisition Information
Accession 51127 transferred by the Office of the Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 8 January 2014.
Biographical/Historical Information
In 1970, the Governor's Management Commission Study recommended the creation of six "Deputy Governors" to assist the Chief Executive in his managerial duties. Compatible functions of government were grouped under these administrative heads, who would serve as the Governor's top management team or "secretariats" as they are called now. Currently there are 8 secretariats in state government, which are: the Secretary of Administration; Secretary of Commerce and Trade; Secretary of Education; Secretary of Finance; Secretary of Health and Human Resources; Secretary of Natural Resources; Secretary of Public Safety; Secretary of Transportation.
The secretariat responsible for human services, health and welfare has gone through several reorganizations. In 1972, the General Assembly passed an act establishing the Secretary of Human Affairs. This office was responsible for management and direction of health and human services provided by the state for the citizens of the commonwealth. In 1976, the secretariat's name changed to the Secretary of Human Resources. With reorganization of state government, the secretariat name changed again to the Secretary of Health and Human Resources in 1988. The Secretary of Health and Human Resources oversees state agencies which provide services to Virginians with mental retardation, mental illness, substance abuse and physical disability concerns, and provide assistance to low-income families and to the aging community. Additionally, the agencies also license health practitioners and ensure safe drinking water in the Commonwealth.
William A. "Bill" Hazel, an orthopaedic surgeon, served as Secretary of Health and Human Resources during the McDonnell Administration. After earning a degree in civil engineering from Princeton University, Dr. Hazel attended Duke University School of Medicine and completed his orthopaedic residency at the Mayo Clinic. He is a founding member of Commonwealth Orthopaedics and Rehabilitation, a medical practice with facilities located across Northern Virginia. He is a former assistant orthopaedic surgeon for the Washington Redskins and team physician for the D.C. United soccer team. As Secretary, Dr. Hazel oversaw twelve state agencies and boards: Assistive Technology Loan Fund Authority; Dept. for the Aging and Rehabilitative Services; Dept. of Behavioral Health and Developmental Services; Dept. for the Blind and Vision Impaired; Dept. for the Deaf and Hard of Hearing; Dept. of Health; Dept. of Health Professions; Dept. of Medical Assistance Services; Dept. of Social Services; Board for People with Disabilities; Office of the Comprehensive Services Act; and Virginia Foundation for Healthy Youth.
Other staff members in the Office of the Secretary of Health and Human Services during the McDonnell Administration include Deputy Secretaries Matt Cobb and Keith Hare; Assistant Secretary of Children's Health and Education, Karin Addison; Director of Community Relations, Judy Ahern; Director of the Virginia Health Reform Initiative, Cynthia B. Jones; Deputy Director of the Virginia Health Reform Initiative, Molly Huffstetler; Director of the Office of Health Information Technology, Kim Barnes; and Homeless Outcomes Coordinator, Kristin Burhop. Major accomplishments for the Secretary of Health and Human Resources during the McDonnel Administration include the creation of the Virginia Center for Health Innovation (VHRI), negotiation of an agreement with the Dept. of Justice to improve service for individuals with developmental disabilities, and the initiation of an enterprise IT system transformation for health and human services.
Scope and Content
Contains records created and maintained by Secretary of Health and Human Resources, Dr. Bill Hazel, during the administration of Governor Robert McDonnell. The records include Correspondence of the Office of the Secretary, Constituent Correspondence, Regulations, Scheduling requests, and Special Project files, which consist of incoming and outgoing correspondence, regulations, subject files, legislative files, budget material, and records related to activities and special projects.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary, 2010-2013
Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Constituents, 2010-2013
Series III. Regulations, 2010-2012
Series IV. Scheduling requests, 2010-2013
Series V. Special Projects and Studies, 2010-2013.
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary, 2010-2013., Extent: 2.1 cu. ft. (6 boxes).
  Correspondence of the Secretary, 2010-2013, contains incoming and outgoing correspondence and related attachments from local, state and federal government officials, state and federal legislators, business owners, healthcare providers, and associations, as well as constituent correspondence sent directly to the Office of the Secretary of Health and Human Resources. Topics include environmental health, health insurance, legislation, lyme disease, Medicaid, mental health facilities, and social services, among others.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Ab-Am, 2010-2013. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - An-Ay, 2010-2013. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ba, 2010-2013. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Be, 2010-2013. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bi, 2010-2013. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bl, 2010-2013. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bo, 2010-2013. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Br, 2010-2013. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bu-By, 2010-2013. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Ca, 2010-2013. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Ch, 2010-2013. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cl-Cof, 2010-2013. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Col-Cu, 2010-2013. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Da-De, 2010-2013. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Di-Du, 2010-2013. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - E, 2010-2013. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - F, 2010-2013. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Ga-Gl, 2010-2013. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Go-Gr, 2010-2013. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ha, 2010-2013. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - He, 2010-2013. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Hi, 2010-2013. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Ho, 2010-2013. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Hu-Hy, 2010-2013. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - I, 2010-2013. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Ja-Je, 2010-2013. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Jo-Ju, 2010-2013. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Ka-Kirm, 2010-2013. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Kirs-Ku, 2010-2013. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - La-Le, 2010-2013. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Li-Ly, 2010-2013. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Ma, 2010-2013. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Mc, 2010-2013. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Me-Mi, 2010-2013. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Mo, 2010-2013. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Mu, 2010-2013. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - N, 2010-2013. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - O, 2010-2013. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pa-Pi, 2010-2013. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Po-Pu, 2010-2013. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Ra-Ri, 2010-2013. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Ro-Ru, 2010-2013. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Sa-Se, 2010-2013. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Sh-Si, 2010-2013. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Sm-St, 2010-2013. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Su-Sy, 2010-2013. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Ta-Th, 2010-2013. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - To-Tu, 2010-2013. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - U-V, 2010-2013. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Wa-We, 2010-2013. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Wh-Wi, 2010-2013. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Wo-Wy, 2010-2013. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Y-Z, 2010-2013. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Constituents, 2005-2009., Extent: 1.05 cu. ft. (3 boxes).
  Contains incoming correspondence from constituents and other non-governmental entities sent directly to the Secretary of Health and Human Resources or referred to the Secretary from the Office of the Governor for response. Also included is the outgoing correspondence from the Secretary as well as supporting documentation and correspondence from related agency officials. Topics include health insurance, Dept. of Social Services, Medicaid, legislation, environmental health, mental health facilities, and Lyme disease.
  Arranged numerically by database number which is generally chronological by date of response letter.
  - 2000180-2011716, 2010 Jan-June. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 2013292-2018899, 2010 Mar-May. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 2019540-2022494, 2010 Mar-Apr. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 2023340-2042429, 2010 Mar-May. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 2047200-2055999, 2010 May-June. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 2056182-2059955, 2010 June. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 2060013-2061321, 2010 June. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 2061467-2063900, 2010 June-July. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 2064114-2066996, 2010 July. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 2067096-2068517, 2010 Aug. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 2069284-2083630, 2010 Aug-Sept. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 2084124-2091185, 2010 Sept-Oct. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 2092240-2084802, 2010 Oct-Nov. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 2095240-2096921, 2010 Oct-Nov. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 2097367-2100066, 2010 Nov-Dec. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 2100165-2102842, 2010 Dec-2011 Jan. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 2103036-2104912, 2011 Jan. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 2105212-2105798, 2011 Jan-Feb. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 2106087-2107774, 2011 Feb. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 2108120-2109776, 2011 Feb-June. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 2110030-2114716, 2011 Feb-Mar. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 2115029-2116853, 2011 Mar. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 2117016-2120475, 2011 Mar-May. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 2121282-2125835, 2011 Mar-May. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 2126052-2128693, 2011 May-June. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 2129305-2130726, 2011 June. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 2131268-2132493, 2011 June-July. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 2133068-2136890, 2011 July-Aug. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 2137088-2139988, 2011 Aug-Sept. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 2140328-2142878, 2011 Sept-Oct. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 2143233-2146612, 2011 Oct. (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Series III. Regulations, 2010-2012., Extent: 1.15 cu. ft. (3 boxes).
  Regulations, 2010-2012, are limited to the licensure of abortion facilities and the ultrasound requirement as part of informed consent for abortion (HB 462), 2012. Files include agendas, correspondence, legislation, memoranda, petitions, publications, regulations, and reports.
  - Licensure of abortion facilities, 2010-2011. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Licensure of abortion facilities, 2010-2011. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Licensure of abortion facilities, 2011. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Licensure of abortion facilities, 2011-2012. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Licensure of abortion facilities - Agenda (State Board of Health meeting), 2011 Aug. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Licensure of abortion facilities - Agenda (State Board of Health meeting), 2012 Dec. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Licensure of abortion facilities - Bills (House), 2011. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Licensure of abortion facilities - Bills (SB124), 2011. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Licensure of abortion facilities - Clinical procedures, 2011. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Licensure of abortion facilities - Petitions, undated. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Licensure of abortion facilities - Petitions, undated. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Licensure of abortion facilities - Petitions, undated. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Licensure of abortion facilities - Petitions, undated. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Licensure of abortion facilities - Petitions, undated. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Licensure of abortion facilities - Petitions, undated. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Licensure of abortion facilities - Publications, 2010. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Licensure of abortion facilities - Ultrasound requirement as part of informed consent (HB462), 2012. (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Series VIII. Scheduling requests, 2010-2013., Extent: .7 cu. ft. (2 boxes).
  Scheduling requests, 2010-2013, document requests to the Secretary for meetings or attendance at events. Includes correspondence, invitations, event information and logistics, and programs related to conferences, luncheons, meetings, receptions, and tours. The majority of events are related to aging, drug addiction, healthcare, mental health, public health, wellness and the disabled.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Scheduling requests, 2010 Feb. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Scheduling requests, 2010 Mar. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Scheduling requests, 2010 Apr. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Scheduling requests, 2010 May. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Scheduling requests, 2010 June. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Scheduling requests, 2010 July. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Scheduling requests, 2010 Aug. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Scheduling requests, 2010 Oct. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Scheduling requests, 2010 Nov. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Scheduling requests, 2010 Dec. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Scheduling requests, 2011 Jan. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Scheduling requests, 2011 Feb. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Scheduling requests, 2011 Mar. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Scheduling requests, 2011 Apr. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Scheduling requests, 2011 May. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Scheduling requests, 2011 June. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Scheduling requests, 2011 July-Sept. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Scheduling requests, 2011 Oct. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Scheduling requests, 2011 Nov-Dec. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Scheduling requests, 2012 Jan-Feb. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Scheduling requests, 2012 Mar-Apr. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Scheduling requests, 2012 May-Nov. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Scheduling requests, 2013 Jan-Mar. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Scheduling requests, 2013 Apr-July. (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Series IX. Special Projects and Studies, 2010-2013., Extent: 3.5 cu. ft. (10 boxes).
  Special Project and Studies, 2010-2013, contains a variety of files pertaining to special projects and task forces such as the State Executive Council for the Comprehensive Services Act, Developmental Disabilities Services System, Homeless Outcomes Advisory Committee / Homelessness Project and the Virginia Health Reform Initiative, among others. Files include correspondence, legislation, meeting records, memoranda, presentations and reports.
  - Albro, Dave - H.B. 382, 2008. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Central Virginia Training Center, 2010-2011. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Central Virginia Training Center, 2010. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Central Virginia Training Center, 2011. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Adoptions (DSS), 2011. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Centralized billing (DMAS), 2011. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Children's Mental Health (DBHDS), 2010. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Children's Mental Health (DBHDS), 2011. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Children's Mental Health (DBHDS), 2011-2012. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Children's Services Transformation, 20111. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Commission on Youth / Kinship Caregivers, 2010-2011. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Commission on Youth / Kinship Caregivers, 2012. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Health Innovation, 2013. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Independent Living (DSS), 201. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Intensive Care Coordination, 2010. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Managing by data, 2011. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Office of Comprehensiver Service / Executive Director Reogranization, undated. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Public / Private Partnerships (DSS), 2010. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Social Services, Dept. of, 2010-2012. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State and Local Advisory Team (SLAT), 2010 Nov 4. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State and Local Advisory Team (SLAT), 2011 Mar 3. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State and Local Advisory Team (SLAT), 2011 May 5. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State and Local Advisory Team (SLAT), 2011 July 7. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State and Local Advisory Team (SLAT) / Training workshop, 2011 Sept 28. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State and Local Advisory Team (SLAT), 2013 June 6. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State and Local Advisory Team (SLAT), 2013 Aug 1. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State Executive Council, 2010 Sept 30. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State Executive Council / Pittsylvania County, 2010. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State Executive Council, 2011 Mar 31. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State Executive Council / Retreat, 201 May 16. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State Executive Council, 2011 Dec 5. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State Executive Council, 2011 June 6. (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State Executive Council / Retreat, 2012 Sept 20. (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State Executive Council, 2013 Apr 30. (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State Executive Council (Executive Committee and SLAT Executive Committee), 2013 May 8. (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State Executive Council, 2013 July 13. (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State Executive Council / Denial of funds, 2011. (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State Executive Council / Informational items, 2011. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State Executive Council / Miscellaneous, 2010-2013. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - State Executive Council / Orientation, 2010. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Systems of care (DSS), 2010-2013. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Systems of care (DSS) / Scholarships, 2011. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Systems of care (DSS) / Scholarships, 2012. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Systems of care (DSS) / Scholarships, 2013. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Systems of care (DSS) / Scholarships, undated. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Training, 2010-2011. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Comprehensive Services Act - Transition Age Youth, 201. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Developmental Disabilities Services System (DOJ), 2011-2012. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Developmental Disabilities Services System (DOJ), 20111-2012. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Developmental Disabilities Services System (DOJ), 2012. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Fair hearing review, 2010-2012. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 20102012. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Hancock Geriatric Treatment Center, 2010. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Hancock Geriatric Treatment Center, 2010-2011. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Hancock Geriatric Treatment Center, 2010-2011. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Homelessness Project, 2012-2013. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Homelessness Project - Access to Substance Abuse and Mental Health Treatment Subcommittee, 2013. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Homelessness Project - Advisory Committee, 2012. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Homelessness Project - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of, 2011-2012. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Homelessness Project - Blueprint for Livable Communities Advisory Group (DARS), 2013. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Homelessness Project - Business and Funder Leadership Council on Homelessness, Virginia, 2012. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Homelessness Project - Catawba Regional Partnership, 2012. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Homelessness Project - Central Intake, 2012. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Homelessness Project - Daily Planet, undated. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Homelessness Project - Dashboard, 2013. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Homelessness Project - Data Collection and System Coordination Committee, 2013. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Homelessness Project - Employing people experiencing homelessness, 2012. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Homelessness Project - Ending family and youth homelessness, 2013. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Homelessness Project - Governor's Housing Conference, 2012. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Homelessness Project - Governor's Housing Conference, 2013. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Homelessness Project - Health, Dept. of, 2012. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Homelessness Project - HEARTH Act, 2012. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Homelessness Project - Homeward, 2012. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Homelessness Project - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 2012. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Homelessness Project - Housing Policy Workgroup and Advisory Committee, 2012. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Homelessness Project - Juvenile Justice, Dept. of and Corrections, Dept. of, 2012. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Homelessness Project - Meeting with Gov. McDonnell, 2013. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Homelessness Project - National Alliance to End Homelessness Conference, 2012. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Homelessness Project - National Alliance to End Homelessness Leadership Council, 2012-2013. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Homelessness Project - Norfolk Dept. of Human Services, 2012. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Homelessness Project - Homlessness press conference (The Road to Ending Homelessness), 2013. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Homelessness Project - Rapid Results Institute, 2012. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Homelessness Project - Richmond Housing Trust Fund, undated. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Homelessness Project - Social Services, Dept. of, 2012. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Homelessness Project - Supportive Services and Funding Committee, 2013. (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Homelessness Project - Temporary Assitance for Needy Families (TANF) and Rapid Re-housing in Virginia, 2013. (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Homelessness Project - The Healing Place, 2013. (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Homelessness Project - Veterans Services, Dept. of, 2012-2013. (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Homelessness Project - Virginia Association of Housing Counselors Conference, 2013. (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Homelessness Project - Virginia Association of Local Human Services Officials Conference, 2012. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Homelessness Project - Virginia Coalition to End Homelessness and DBHDS Housing Stability and Mental Illness Summit, 2012. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Homelessness Project - Virginia Homeless Veterans Summit, 2012. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Homelessness Project - Virginia Hospital and Health Information Association Behavioral Health Forum, 2012-2013. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Homelessness Project - Virginia Housing Development Authority, 2012. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Homelessness Project - Virginia Supportive Housing, 2012. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Homelessness Project - Workplace Development Work Group, 2013. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Lyme Disease Task Force, 2010-2011. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of - Union payments, 2010. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous handwritten notes, 2010-2013. (Box 22, Folder 10)